Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Departments, 1999-2014; Series II
  - Member Services Department
    - Newsletters
      - Newsletter, volume 57, numbers 1-11, 2009 November - 2010 October (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - Newsletter, volume 58, numbers 1-11, 2010 November - 2011 October (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - Newsletter, volume 59, numbers 1-11, 2011 November - 2012 October (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Annual conference
      Subseries includes 2 copies of record of each Summary of Proceedings.
      - Summary of Proceedings: 60th Annual Conference - Chicago, 2006 June 21-14 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 61st Annual Conference - Philadelphia, 2007 June 13-16 (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 62nd Annual Conference - Ottawa, 2008 June 25-28 (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Annual conference program and registration materials, 2008 June 25-28 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 63rd Annual Conference - St. Louis, 2009 June 17-20 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - Correspondence re: 2009 annual conference Vice-Presidential invitational luncheon, 2009 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 132)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 64th Annual Conference - Louisville, 2010 June 16-19 (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 65th Annual Conference - Chicago, 2011 June 8-11 (Box 5, Folder 134)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 66th Annual Conference - Scottsdale, 2012 June 27-30 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - ATLA Serials Exchange
      ATLA Serials Exchange program formerly known as Library Materials Exchange program
      - Planning correspondence, 1999 December 7 - 2002 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - Net meeting chat logs for online planning meetings, 1999 December 10 - 2000 February 23 (Box 6, Folder 137)
      - Database proposals/designs and summary of ATLA Serials Exchange program, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 138)
      - Correspondence re: reimbursement limit for postage, 2001 May 2 - October 26 (Box 6, Folder 139)
      - Beta test of ATLA Serials Exchange, 2001 OCtober 19 - Novmber 12 (Box 6, Folder 140)
      - Mailing to announce start of ATLA Serials Exchange, 2001 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Correspondence, 2001 June 29 - 2003 June 6 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Member publications
      - Theological Librarianship Journal
        - Online journal, volume 1, number 1, 2008 June (Box 7, Folder 152)
        - Online journal, volume 1, number 2, 2008 December (Box 7, Folder 153)
        - Online journal, volume 2, number 1, 2009 June (Box 7, Folder 154)
        - Online journal, volume 2, number 2, 2009 December (Box 7, Folder 155)
        - Online journal, volume 3, number 1, 2010 June (Box 7, Folder 156)
        - Online journal, volume 3, number 2, 2010 December (Box 7, Folder 157)
        - Online journal, volume 4, number 1, 2011 July (Box 7, Folder 158)
        - Online journal, volume 5, number 1, 2012 June (Box 7, Folder 159)
      - ATLA website
        - Pages re: student chapters, 2003 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 160)
        - Preservation department pages, 2006 February 20 (Box 8, Folder 161)
        - ATLA online catalog 2006-2007, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 162)
        - ATLA preservation program catalog online, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 163)
        - Catholic periodical and literature Index user's guide, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 164)
        - Cooperative digital resources initiative pages, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 165)
        - Frequently asked questions pages, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 166)
        - Holdings of journals indexed in ATLA RDB, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 167)
        - Index to book reviews in Religion, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 168)
        - Old testament abstracts, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 169)
        - Product news pages, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 170)
        - Research in ministry online pages, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 171)
        - Technical support pages, 2006 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 172)
        - Member services pages, 2009 February 18 (Box 8, Folder 176)
      - Weekly news updates
        - Weekly news updates 2006 (Box 8, Folder 173)
        - Weekly news updates 2007 (Box 8, Folder 174)
        - Weekly news udpates 2008 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Preservation Department
    - Emails regarding articles and preservation, 2000 March - April (Box 8, Folder 177)
- Committees of the Association, 2000-2007; Series III
  - Committees appointed by the Executive Director
    - Annual Conference Committee
      - Correspondence, 2000 January - July (Box 9, Folder 178)
      - Correspondence, 2000 August - November (Box 9, Folder 179)
      - Correspondence, 2001 January - August (Box 9, Folder 180)
      - Correspondence, 2001 September - December (Box 9, Folder 181)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 182)
      - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 183)
      - Meeting agendas and minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 184)
      - Meeting agendas and minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 185)
      - Meeting agendas and minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 186)
      - Planning materials, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 187)
      - Planning materials, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 188)
      - Planning materials, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 189)
      - Planning materials, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 190)
      - Planning materials, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - Education Committee
      - Meeting agenda, minutes, and agenda items, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 192)
      - Meeting agendas and planning materials, 2005, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Emergency Response Team Committee
      - Correspondence, 2002, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 194)
      - Meeting minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Endowment Committee
      - Retirees binder, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Enterprise Content Management Committee
      - Request for Information, 2007 June (Box 10, Folder 197)
      - Meeting minutes, 2007 July - November (Box 10, Folder system_indicator_aaae2af5cdfcfa97b3ef28cb46f666fd)
      - Task force charge and Request for Information, 2007 August (Box 10, Folder 199)
      - Report, 2007 November 15 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - Historic Records/Archives Committee
      - Correspondence and guidelines, 2000 March 7 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - International Collaboration Committee
      - Reports, correspondence, meeting minutes and materials., 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 202)
      - Reports, correspondence, meeting minutes and materials, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 203)
      - Reports, correspondence, meeting minutes and materials, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 204)
        Includes CD-ROM.
      - Reports, correspondence, meeting minutes and materials, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Local Host Committee
      - Committee meeting notes, 2006 October 25-26 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Professional Development Committee
      - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 207)
      - Correspondene, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 208)
      - Meeting minutes, 2000 June 22, 23 (Box 10, Folder 209)
      - Professional development questionnaire and results, 2000 October 16 (Box 10, Folder 210)
      - Regional grant materials and correspondence, committee summary of activites, 2000 August - 2001 January (Box 10, Folder 211)
      - Regional program speakers materials and correspondence, 2001 April 18-20 (Box 10, Folder 212)
      - Management issues seminar, meeting minutes and committee fact sheet, 2001 May 30 - 2001 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 213)
      - Continuing education grants materials and correspondence, 2001 December 6-20 (Box 11, Folder 214)
      - Theological resources seminar materials, 2002 January 9 (Box 11, Folder 215)
      - IMLS grant proposal materials and correspondence, 2003 November (Box 11, Folder 216)
    - Publication Committee
      - Committee proposal, notes and minutes, 2001-2007 (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Supervisor Evaluation Task Force Committee
      - Committee proposal and correspondence, 2002 August-2003 March (Box 11, Folder 218)
      - Annual upward evaluation materials and correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 219)
  - Joint Committees established by the Board
    - Committee on Standards for Regional Groups in ATLA
      - Regional group materials, surveys and survey summary, 2001 March-2001 June (Box 11, Folder 220)
  - Advisory Committees
    - Preservation Advisory Committee
      - Correspondence, 1999-2005 (Box 11, Folder 221)
      - Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 222)
    - Technology Advisory Committee
      - Interactive conference facility materials and correspondence, 2001 September-October (Box 11, Folder 223)
  - Special Committees and Standing Committees of the Board
    - Nominating Committee
      - Board of Directors ballots, 1997-2004 (Box 11, Folder 224)
      - Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - Teller's Committee
      - Reports re: election results, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - ATLA/ATS Digital Standards and Projects Committee
      - Minutes, reports, publicity, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 229)
- Interest Groups, 2000-2012; Series IV
  - General
    - Interest group handbook and correspondence, 2003-2009 (Box 11, Folder 227)
  - Automation and Technology
    - Statistics task force materials and correspondence, 2003-2008 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - Collection Evaluation and Development
    - Correspondence, 2003 February 26-March 4 (Box 11, Folder 230)
  - College and University
    - Correspondence, 2003 Februrary 27 (Box 11, Folder 231)
  - Lesbian and Gay
    - Correspondence, 2003 February 26-March 3 (Box 11, Folder 232)
  - OCLC Theological Users Group
    - Correspondence, 2003 February 26-May 3 (Box 11, Folder 233)
  - Public Services
    - Correspondence, 2003 February 26 (Box 11, Folder 234)
  - Publications
    - Correspondence and materials, 1994-2004 (Box 11, Folder 235)
  - Technical Services
    - Theology Cataloging Bulletin
      - Volume 8, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 236)
        Missing issue number 1, November 1999.
      - Volume 9, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 237)
      - Volume 10, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 238)
      - Volume 11, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 239)
      - Volume 12, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 240)
      - Volume 13, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 241)
      - Volume 14, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 242)
      - Volume 15, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 243)
      - Volume 16, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 244)
      - Volume 17, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 245)
      - Volume 18, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 246)
      - Volume 19, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 247)
      - Volume 20, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 248)
- Affiliated Institutions and Organizations, 2010; Series V
  - Biblioteques Europeennes de Theologie (BETH) brochure, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 249)
- Photographs and Ephemera, 2000-2004; Series VI
  - Photographs: ATLA staff, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 250)
  - Photographs: Conferences, 2001-2006 (Box 13, Folder 251)
  - Ephemera: conference bag, coasters, 2003, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 252)